canadianbusinessdirectory.ca 2006-06-17

# Privacy Policy - canadianbusinessdirectory.ca

  |  |  **  
  Home Page

  Browse By Location

  Browse By Categories

  Search

  Advertise With Us

  Contact Us

  Your Account

  Business Tools

  Latest Additions

  Link To Us

  Add To Favorites

** |  | 

>   
> 
> 
> ### Privacy Policy - canadianbusinessdirectory.ca
> 
> **This Privacy Policy** applies to the services offered on the canadianbusinessdirectory.ca web site offered by canadianbusinessdirectory.ca . Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before using the canadianbusinessdirectory.ca web site. Usage of the canadianbusinessdirectory.ca website is conditional upon you agreeing to be bound by this privacy policy. 
> 
> In summary, while you should read each provision in this Privacy Policy, you must note that by using the canadianbusinessdirectory.ca website: 
> 
> you agree that if you disclose your personal information to us for the purpose of our **Canadian Business Directory** listing, we will create a database record about you and make the directory listing accessible on our website; you agree for us to contact you with information about products and services which may be of interest to you and your continued use of the website indicates your agreement with any future changes in the canadianbusinessdirectory.ca Privacy Policy. 
> 
> **1\. Collecting information about you**   
> canadianbusinessdirectory.ca collects information for its directory listings from publicly available sources and from businesses themselves. canadianbusinessdirectory.ca will not otherwise collect or monitor any personal information about you without your consent. When you submit information on our website, we ask for you to provide an email address and collect your Internet Protocol number which indicates the server through which you are accessing the internet. We collect this information in order to verify any details which you provide to us. 
> 
> **2\. Using and disclosing your personal information**   
> Our purpose in collecting information about you or your business is to provide you with profile and with customer contacts through listing this information in a directory. By submitting information to our website you agree for this information to be listed in the directory on our website. 
> 
> **3\. When we will contact you?**   
> We may from time to time contact you at the email or other address which you provide to us in order to: 
> 
> * Provide you with updated information about our website 
> * Provide you with other information about our products and services which may be of interest to you. 
> 
> If you are receiving promotional information about canadianbusinessdirectory.ca and do not wish to receive this information any longer, you may email us at info@canadianbusinessdirectory.ca and ask to be removed from our mailing list. Please allow 2 weeks for this request to be processed. 
> 
> **4\. You can access the information we keep about you**   
> The directory shows what information we hold about you. You are welcome to check if we hold any other personal information about you by e-mailing us at info@canadianbusinessdirectory.ca . Our record of your information will be made available to you within 2 weeks. 
> 
> **5\. Changing and deleting the information we have about you**   
> If at any time you wish to change a listing that is inaccurate or out of date, then: 
> 
> * If you have your email and password you can login and change your information. 
> * Send an email to info@canadianbusinessdirectory.ca and request a password 
> * Send an email to info@canadianbusinessdirectory.ca and request the change, please allow 2 weeks for your profile to be updated. 
> 
> **6\. Storage and security of your personal information**   
> canadianbusinessdirectory.ca will do best to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. Please note also that canadianbusinessdirectory.ca. 
> 
> **7\. canadianbusinessdirectory.ca and links to other websites**   
> canadianbusinessdirectory.ca provides links to websites outside of the canadianbusinessdirectory.ca service. These linked sites are not under the control of canadianbusinessdirectory.ca, and we are not responsible for the conduct of companies linked to our website. 
> 
> **8\. What to do if you have a problem or question**   
> If canadianbusinessdirectory.ca becomes aware of any ongoing concerns or problems with sites on our website, we will take these issues seriously and work to address these concerns. If you have any further queries relating to our Privacy Policy, or you have a problem or complaint, please contact us at info@canadianbusinessdirectory.ca. 
> 
> **9\. Future changes**   
> Our commitment to be a leading provider of online directory services means that our business will continue to evolve as we introduce new services and features to our website. Because of this, from time to time, our policies will be reviewed and may be revised. canadianbusinessdirectory.ca. reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time and notify you by posting an updated version of the policy on its website. The amended Privacy Policy will apply between us whether or not we have given you specific notice of any change. 

|  |
